http://chefmall.com/privacy-policy/

Loading... Please wait...
All prices are in USD
Shopping Cart
Menu
Compare (0 Item)
Kenkut For Home Chefs
Kenkut Dispenser Parts Dept.
Kenkut For Home Chefs
Kenkut Dispenser Parts Dept.
Privacy Policy
Chefmall.com is dedicated to providing our customers with exemplary customer service that includes protecting your privacy. Please review our Privacy Policy below and feel free to contact us with any questions or concerns.Chefmall.comPrivacy PolicyOur Commitment To Privacy Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.The Information We Collect: This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on the Chefmall.com Web site. On some pages, you can order products, make requests, and register to receive materials. The types of personal information collected at these pages are:
Name
Address
Email address
Phone number
Credit/Debit Card Information
(etc.)
On some pages, you can submit information about other people. For example, if you order a gift online and want it sent directly to the recipient, you will need to submit the recipient's address. In this circumstance, the types of personal information collected are:
Name
Address
Phone Number
(etc.)
The Way We Use Information: We use the information you provide about yourself when placing an order only to complete that order. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order.We use the information you provide about someone else when placing an order only to ship the product and to confirm delivery. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order.We use return email addresses to answer the email we receive. Such addresses are not used for any other purpose and are not shared with outside parties.You can register with our Web site if you would like to receive our catalog as well as updates on our new products and services. Information you submit on our Web site will not be used for this purpose unless you fill out the registration form or place an order with us.We use non-identifying and aggregate information to better design our Web site and to share with advertisers. For example, we may tell an advertiser that X number of individuals visited a certain area on our Web site, or that Y number of men and Z number of women filled out our registration form, but we would not disclose anything that could be used to identify those individuals.Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses.Our Commitment To Data Security To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.Our Commitment To Children's Privacy: Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our Web site from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our Web site is structured to attract anyone under 13.How You Can Access Or Correct Your Information You can access all your personally identifiable information that we collect online and maintain by contacting us directly. We use this procedure to better safeguard your information. You can correct factual errors in your personally identifiable information by sending us a request that credibly shows error.To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections
Sign up for our newsletter
Name
Email
Copyright 2020 --Chefmall Store. All Rights Reserved. | Sitemap |
Bigcommerce Premium Themes by PSDCenter
All prices are in USD
